Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
s9ss1ss3ss6">T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - Second Alpha Sequence A-Z
        - Adé, Sunny - Vol. 4 Late General Ramat Muritala Mohammed, 1976; SR-21283; Adé, Sunny; Sunny Ade & His African Beats (Box 91)
          Catalog # SALPS 4; A-side Matrix # ADE 7 JS1
          Decca
          France
        - Africanism - "Edony" clap your hands; Call it jungle jazz, 2000; SR-21284; Africanism (Box 91)
          Catalog # YP080; A-side Matrix # YP 080 A NiLZ - THE EXCHANGE DFI-00-9
          Yellow Productions
          Paris, France
        - Agent Provocateur - Red tape, 1995; SR-21285; Agent Provocateur (Box 91)
          Catalog # WALL T 017 - A1; A-side Matrix # WALL T 017 - A1 MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE
          Wall of Sound
          London, England
        - Ambersunshower - Walter T., 1996; SR-21286; Ambersunshower (Box 91)
          Catalog # GEET 66; A-side Matrix # GEET 66 A SIMON-THE EXCHANGE
          Gee Street
          United Kingdom
        - Area Code (212) - Extension from Area Code (212), 1979; SR-21287; Area Code (212) (Box 91)
          Catalog # FS114; A-side Matrix # 31041 A-2
          Friends & Co.
          New York, New York
        - Arrow - Keep on jamming, 1976; SR-21288; Arrow; Mighty Arrow (Box 91)
          Catalog # LPS-008; A-side Matrix # LPS-008-S1
          Charlie's Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Atmospheres - Voyage to Uranus, 1974; SR-21289; Atmospheres; Stevens, Clive (Box 91)
          Catalog # SM-11676; A-side Matrix # SM-1-11676 H-1 #1
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Bassplugger - Sumac, 2002; SR-21290; Bassplugger (Box 91)
          Catalog # beatnix-003; A-side Matrix # Beatnix-003-A PUSHING BEATS UNTIL THEY BREAK
          Beatnix Labs Recordings
          Santa Barbara, California
        - Bekombo, Féfé - Africa-Wonderful, 1988; SR-21291; Bekombo, Féfé (Box 91)
          Catalog # TN 598; A-side Matrix # FEFE A TN598 A
          Production TN
        - Brown, James - The payback mix, 1988; SR-28826; Brown, James (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-28827. Different discs.
          Catalog # 887-852-1; A-side Matrix # 887-852-1-AS-SP
          Polydor
        - Brown, James - Payback (the final mixdown), 1988; SR-28827; Brown, James (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-28826. Different discs.
          Catalog # URBA 17; A-side Matrix # URB 17 A RE1
          Urban
        - Brown, James - Sex machine (recorded live at home in Augusta, Georgia with his bad self) (Disc one), 1977; SR-28828; Brown, James (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-28829; SR-28830. Double album.
          Catalog # PD-2-9004; A-side Matrix # PD-2-9004-AS-CPX
        - Brown, James - Sex machine (recorded live at home in Augusta, Georgia with his bad self) (Disc one), 1977; SR-28829; Brown, James (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-28828; SR-28830. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PD-2-9004; A-side Matrix # PD-2-90041 S-CP
        - Brown, James - Sex machine (recorded live at home in Augusta, Georgia with his bad self) (Disc two), 1977; SR-28830; Brown, James (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-28828; SR-28829. Double album.
          Catalog # PD-2-9004; A-side Matrix # PD-2-9004-CS-CPX
        - Brown, James - Revolution of the mind (recorded live at the Apollo-vol. III) (Disc two), 1971; SR-28831; Brown, James (Box 91)
          Catalog # PD-3003; A-side Matrix # POLP-80249-1A
        - Brown Sugar - So lovely, 1996; SR-28832; Brown Sugar (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-28833. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NTR 006; A-side Matrix # NTR 006
          Nightown Records
          Germany
        - Brown Sugar - So lovely, 1996; SR-28833; Brown Sugar (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-28832. 2 copies.
        - Browne, Tom - Tommy Gun, 1984; SR-21292; Browne, Tom (Box 91)
          Catalog # AL 8-8249; A-side Matrix # AL 88249-SA-RCA 1
          Arista
        - California Raisins - Meet the Raisins!, 1988; SR-27381; California Raisins (Box 91)
          Catalog # 81917-1; A-side Matrix # STA-887 155-D
          Atlantic
        - Chipmunks - Urban Chipmunk, 1981; SR-21293; Chipmunks (Box 91)
          Catalog # AFL1-4027; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4027-A-1S
          RCA
        - Christian & Rizzo - Universe, 1999; SR-21294; Christian & Rizzo; Pre (Box 91)
          Catalog # AV-91; A-side Matrix # AV-91-A
          AV8
        - Climax Blues Band - FM-live (disc one), 1973; SR-21295; Climax Blues Band (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21296. Double album.
          Catalog # SAS-2-7411; A-side Matrix # SAS-2-7411-A-2
          Sire
        - Climax Blues Band - FM-live (disc two), 1973; SR-21296; Climax Blues Band (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21295. Double album.
          Catalog # SAS-2-7411; A-side Matrix # SAS-2-7411-B-2
        - Craig, Robbie - Vol. 2 "Lessons", 1997; SR-21297; Craig, Robbie; NCA; Gurley, Steve; Vice Versa (Box 91)
          Catalog # PPDT25; A-side Matrix # PPDT 25-A
          Public Demand
          Essex, England
        - Crazy B - Genius touch 3, 2001; SR-21298; Crazy B; Faster Jay (Box 91)
          Catalog # GT003; A-side Matrix # GT003 A DFI 01 3 RV-TR
          Genius Touch
        - Crazy B - Genius touch 1, 1998; SR-21299; Crazy B; Faster Jay (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21300. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # GT001; A-side Matrix # GT01 A
        - Crazy B - Genius touch 1, 1998; SR-21300; Crazy B; Faster Jay (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21299. Multiple copies.
        - Crusaders - Scratch, 1974; SR-21301; Crusaders (Box 91)
          Catalog # BTS 6010; A-side Matrix # BTS 6010 6079 X
          Blue Thumb Records
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Danzonera Mexicana de Nelly Jimenez - Merengues y danzones: Salon Mexico, 1960; SR-21302; Danzonera Mexicana de Nelly Jimenez; Quisqueya, Linda; Jimenez, Nelly (Box 91)
          Catalog # EXPLORER-104; A-side Matrix # RE-EXPLORER-104-A
          Explorer
          United States
        - Roy Davis & Jay Juniel - Men from the Nile pt. 2, 1997; SR-21303; Roy Davis & Jay Juniel (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21304. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # UTR-0005; A-side Matrix # BT001-A
          Undaground Therapy Muzik
        - Roy Davis & Jay Juniel - Men from the Nile pt. 2, 1997; SR-21304; Roy Davis & Jay Juniel (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21303. Multiple copies.
        - Def Con 6 - Puttin it on wax EP, 1997; SR-21305; Def Con 6 (Box 91)
          Catalog # TW008; A-side Matrix # TW-008-A
          Tweak! Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Dharma - Soul warrior; Streetsounds, 1999; SR-21306; Dharma; Dice (Box 91)
          Catalog # AC034; A-side Matrix # AC 034-A1
          Audio Couture
          England
        - Dimensional Sound - The big 50 (disc one), 1977; SR-21307; Dimensional Sound (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21308; SR-21309. Triple album.
          Catalog # TEJ 2004; A-side Matrix # TEJ 2004-1A GOL K-8015
          T.E.J. Records
        - Dimensional Sound - The big 50 (disc two), 1977; SR-21308; Dimensional Sound (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21307; SR-21309. Triple album.
          Catalog # TEJ 2004; A-side Matrix # TEJ 2004-2A GOL K-8015
        - Dimensional Sound - The big 50 (disc three), 1977; SR-21309; Dimensional Sound (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21307; SR-21308. Triple album.
          Catalog # TEJ 2004; A-side Matrix # TEJ 2004-3A GOL K-8015
        - DJ Cuca - Equipe dinamite instrumental vol. III, 1991; SR-21345; DJ Cuca (Box 91)
          Catalog # TNT109; A-side Matrix # TNT 109 A
          TNT Records
          Brazil
        - DJ Fashion - Cracker beats vol. X, 1996; SR-21310; DJ Fashion (Box 91)
          Catalog # 71261-1; A-side Matrix # 71261-BEAT
          Slammin' Records
          Fort Lee, New Jersey
        - DJ Food - Jazz breaks volume 2, 1991; SR-21311; DJ Food (Box 91)
          Catalog # zen 3; A-side Matrix # ZEN-3-A
          Ninja Tune
        - DJ Food - Jazz breaks volume 3 (disc one), 1992; SR-21312; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21313. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 4; A-side Matrix # ZEN-4-A1
        - DJ Food - Jazz breaks volume 3 (disc two), 1992; SR-21313; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21312. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 4; A-side Matrix # ZEN-4-C1
        - DJ Food - Jazz breaks volume 4 (disc one), 1993; SR-21314; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21315. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 6; A-side Matrix # ZEN-6-A1 BC2473
        - DJ Food - Jazz breaks volume 4 (disc two), 1993; SR-21315; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21314. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 6; A-side Matrix # ZEN-6-C2 BC2490
        - DJ Food - Jazz breaks volume 5 (disc one), 1994; SR-21316; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21317. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 10; A-side Matrix # ZEN-10-A1
        - DJ Food - Jazz breaks volume 5 (disc two), 1994; SR-21317; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21316. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 10; A-side Matrix # ZEN-10-C1
        - DJ Food - A recipe for disaster (disc one), 1995; SR-21318; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21319. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 20; A-side Matrix # MPO ZEN 20 A1 THE EXCHANGE-NILZ
        - DJ Food - A recipe for disaster (disc two), 1995; SR-21319; DJ Food (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21318. Double album.
          Catalog # zen 20; A-side Matrix # MPO ZEN 20 C1 THE EXCHANGE-NILZ
        - DJ Icey - New year's day mashup, 2001; SR-21320; DJ Icey (Box 91)
          Catalog # TREE SUP 001; A-side Matrix # Tree SUP-001-A-SR
          Tree Records
          Florida
        - DJ Ito Luv - Betta' breaks & beats volume one, 1995; SR-21321; DJ Ito Luv (Box 91)
          Catalog # MSLP 884; A-side Matrix # MSLP 884A
          Music Station
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - DJ Orlando - Wicked guy, 1996; SR-21325; DJ Orlando (Box 91)
          Catalog # L-47747; A-side Matrix # L-47747 WICKED GUY SIDE A
          House Gate Records
        - DJ Oxide - Terminator, 2000; SR-21326; DJ Oxide (Box 91)
          Catalog # [none]; A-side Matrix # [none]
        - DJ Rod Lee - Bombin bitches, 2002; SR-21339; DJ Rod Lee (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21340. Multiple copies. Different jacket
          Catalog # CBR-CK/005; A-side Matrix # 0112x04 A+B
          Baltimore Breakbeat Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - DJ Rod Lee - Bombin bitches, 2002; SR-21340; DJ Rod Lee (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21339. Multiple copies. Different jacket
        - DJ Technics - New club music vol. 2, 2002; SR-21322; DJ Technics (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21323; SR-21324. Different discs.
          Catalog # CBR-BCM-02; A-side Matrix # 0107144-A
        - DJ Rod Lee - EP, 2002; SR-21323; DJ Rod Lee; Lee, Rod; Wonder, Stevie (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21322; SR-21324. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # CBR-CK/009; A-side Matrix # 0112x03-A
        - DJ Rod Lee - EP, 2002; SR-21324; DJ Rod Lee; Lee, Rod; Wonder, Stevie (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21322; SR-21323. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Technics - Flea market tracks volume 2, 2001; SR-21191; DJ Technics (Box 91)
          Catalog # BCM-6; A-side Matrix # 01019107-A
        - DJ Technics - The projects; The perfect match, 2002; SR-21192; DJ Technics (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21193
          Catalog # KOK-14; A-side Matrix # KOK 14 A
          King of Klub
        - DJ Technics - The projects; The perfect match, 2002; SR-21193; DJ Technics (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21192
        - DJ Technics - Can't stand the beat, 1998; SR-21194; DJ Technics (Box 91)
          Catalog # BB-900; A-side Matrix # 9907X17A
        - DJ Technics - I'm cummin mama; Him downstairs remix, 2002; SR-21327; DJ Technics (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21328. Multiple copies. Different jacket
          Catalog # KOK-11; A-side Matrix # KOK-11 A
        - DJ Technics - I'm cummin mama; Him downstairs remix, 2002; SR-21328; DJ Technics (Box 91)
          In same jacket as # SR-21327. Multiple copies. Different jacket
        - DJ Technics - Technics vs. Dukeyman EP, 1999; SR-21329; DJ Technics; Dukeyman (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21330. Multiple copies. Different jacket
          Catalog # CBR-01; A-side Matrix # 9910X34A
        - DJ Technics - Technics vs. Dukeyman EP, 1999; SR-21330; DJ Technics; Dukeyman (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21329. Multiple copies. Different jacket
        - DJ Technics - I'm cummin mama; Him downstairs remix, 2002; SR-21331; DJ Technics (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21332. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Technics - I'm cummin mama; Him downstairs remix, 2002; SR-21332; DJ Technics (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21331. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Technics - Doo dew bumpin; On the radio, 2002; SR-21333; DJ Technics (Box 92)
          Catalog # KOK-10; A-side Matrix # KOK 10 A
        - DJ Technics - King of Klub Recordings presents Technics, 2002; SR-21334; DJ Technics (Box 92)
          Catalog # KOK-5; A-side Matrix # KOK-5 A
        - DJ Technics - I'm cummin mama; Him downstairs remix, 2002; SR-21335; DJ Technics (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21336. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Technics - I'm cummin mama; Him downstairs remix, 2002; SR-21336; DJ Technics (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21335. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Technics - Doo dew bumpin; On the radio, 2002; SR-21337; DJ Technics (Box 92)
        - DJ Technics - Theo EP, 2000; SR-21338; DJ Technics (Box 92)
          Catalog # CBR-BCM/01; A-side Matrix # 0107X43A
        - Dr. York - New, 1987; SR-21341; Dr. York; York, Malachi Z. (Malachi Zador), 1935- (Box 92)
          Catalog # TLLP 4.00406; A-side Matrix # BN C-4. 00 406-A
          Timeless Records
          West Germany
        - Ed Royal & Enne - Hey, brothers!, 2004; SR-21342; Ed Royal & Enne; Sani; All Good Funk Alliance (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21343; SR-21344. Different discs.
          Catalog # IVR 003; A-side Matrix # INVISION 03-A1
          Innvision Records
          Austria
        - All Good Funk Alliance - Pete's sake; Swing the south, 2004; SR-21343; All Good Funk Alliance (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21342; SR-21344. Different discs. Test pressing
          Catalog # AFA-FW4; A-side Matrix # AFA-FW4-A
          Funk Weapons
        - Arrow - Rush hour, 1984; SR-21344; Arrow (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21342; SR-21343. Different discs.
          Catalog # BSR-AR-021; A-side Matrix # ARROW-021 A1
          B's Records
        - Evil 9 - 4 vini - breaks 12 inch, 2002; SR-25115; Evil 9; Evil Nine; Funk Monster (Box 92)
          Catalog # bos 2035; A-side Matrix # BOS 2035 A-1
          Botchit & Scarper
        - Family - The Family, 1985; SR-21346; Family (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21347. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 1-25322; A-side Matrix # 1-25322-A-SHI B-21390-SHI SLM 9849 1-1
          Warner Bros. Records
          Burbank, California
        - Family - The Family, 1985; SR-21347; Family (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21346. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 1-25322; A-side Matrix # 1-25322-A-SR2
        - Fanatik - Wild stylus (disc one), 1997; SR-21348; Fanatik; Babu; Rhettmatic (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21349. Double album.
          Catalog # HTK001; A-side Matrix # HTK 001 A L-49272
          Heratik Productions
          Oakland, California
        - Fanatik - Wild stylus (disc two), 1997; SR-21349; Fanatik; Babu; Rhettmatic (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-21348. Double album.
          Catalog # HTK001; A-side Matrix # HTK 001 C L-49272
        - Farrow, Larry - It's the happiest time of the year, 1979; SR-21350; Farrow, Larry (Box 92)
          Catalog # ST-12021; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12021
        - Fine Young Cannibals - The raw & the remix, 1990; SR-28473; Fine Young Cannibals; FYC (Box 92)
          Catalog # 828 221.1; A-side Matrix # 8282211 A-3U-1-1
          London Records
        - Fog City Productions - Bulldog breaks volume two, 1991; SR-28474; Fog City Productions (Box 92)
          Catalog # BD-002; A-side Matrix # BDLP 002 A L-43135
          Fog City Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Fog City Productions - Bulldog breaks volume three, 1993; SR-28475; Fog City Productions (Box 92)
          Catalog # BDLP 003; A-side Matrix # BD-003 A1 RE 1
        - G Squad - Militant behavior; For richer for poorer, 1999; SR-28476; G Squad (Box 92)
          Catalog # MNB008; A-side Matrix # MN-B008 A-1-1-
          Mix & Blen'
        - Glamco Productions - Glamco Productions presents Jazzy Grooves vol. III, 1992; SR-28477; Glamco Productions (Box 92)
          Catalog # NBR-01; A-side Matrix # NBR-01 A
          New Breed
        - Hayes, Isaac - Tough guys, 1974; SR-28478; Hayes, Isaac (Box 92)
          Catalog # ENS-7504; A-side Matrix # EQ-0608-1A
          Enterprise
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - Igan, Mitch - Windy city theme, 2002; SR-28479; Igan, Mitch (Box 92)
          Catalog # AE 36067; A-side Matrix # AE 36067/A
          Windy City
        - Jazzy Joyce - Paper chaser "run for it", 1999; SR-28480; Jazzy Joyce; DJ Jazzy Joyce (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-28481. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # AV 85; A-side Matrix # AV-85-A
        - Jazzy Joyce - Paper chaser "run for it", 1999; SR-28481; Jazzy Joyce; DJ Jazzy Joyce (Box 92)
        - Klever - Blazing breakbeats volume three - da 5th element, 1995; SR-28482; Klever (Box 92)
          Catalog # MSLP 890; A-side Matrix # MSLP 890A
        - Krafty Kuts - Krafty Kuts presents...finger lickin' funk vol. 1, 2001; SR-28484; Krafty Kuts (Box 92)
          Catalog # FLR019; A-side Matrix # 08 45282 20 1A1 FLR 019
          Finger Lickin' Records
        - Langston, Andrew - Living together, 1978; SR-28485; Langston, Andrew; Ashwood, Arn (Box 92)
          Catalog # RP 101; A-side Matrix # RP-101-A
          RPL
        - Large Joints - X L, 1999; SR-28486; Large Joints (Box 92)
          Catalog # STAR-1; A-side Matrix # STAR-1-A
          Large Joints
        - Life, Theodore - Somethin' that you do to me, 1981; SR-28487; Life, Theodore; T. Life (Box 92)
          Catalog # AL 9561; A-side Matrix # 1T AL-9561-SA CT-2
        - Lionrock - She's on the train, 1997; SR-28488; Lionrock (Box 92)
          Catalog # 74321 49876 1; A-side Matrix # (TRAIN-1) 74321-49876-1-A THE EXCHANGE NILZ
          Deconstruction
        - Lulu Temple - Don't say no, 1983; SR-28489; Lulu Temple (Box 92)
          Catalog # 5C 38552; A-side Matrix # P AL 38552-1A
          Columbia
        - Mancini, Henry - The Pink Panther Strikes Again (original motion picture soundtrack), 1976; SR-28490; Mancini, Henry (Box 92)
          Catalog # UA-LA694-G; A-side Matrix # UA-LA-694-1
          United Artists Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - McQuilkin, Elwyn - Jour Ouvert, 1982; SR-28491; McQuilkin, Elwyn; Black Wizard (Box 92)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # RAY 002-2-A
          The Kingdom of the Wizards
          Grenada
        - Mission Cartel - Vinyl hedz, 2001; SR-28492; Mission Cartel; DJ 2 Fresh; DJ Quest (Box 92)
          Catalog # BA-001; A-side Matrix # BA-001 A1 6020-1(2)
          Breaks Ahead
        - Nightmares On Wax - Smokers delight (disc one), 1995; SR-28493; Nightmares On Wax (Box 92)
          Catalog # WARP LP 36; A-side Matrix # WARPLP-36-A1
          Warp Records